. 。
.  。
Every time it comes to a critical moment, it turns off the engine.
في كل مرة تأتي فيها لحظة حرجة ، تقوم بإيقاف تشغيل المحرك.
There's something wrong with the soup.
هناك شيء خاطئ في الحساء.
Dog.
كلب.
A puppy?
جرو؟
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
That's great.
ذلك رائع.
Why is it raining?
لماذا تمطر؟
What if
ماذا إذا
it rains?
تمطر؟
Little rabbit,
أرنب صغير
don't be afraid.
لا تخافوا.
We have this.
لدينا هذا.
Are you ready?
هل أنت جاهز؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Let's take shelter from the rain.
لنأخذ مأوى من المطر.
It's still raining,
لا تزال تمطر
Yes.
نعم.
The water is rising.
الماء يرتفع.
Come up! Come up! Come up!
هيا تعال!  هيا تعال!  هيا تعال!
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
I can't drown it.
لا أستطيع أن أغرقها.
My shoes.
حذائي.
Let's
دعونا
go boating.
الذهاب للقوارب.
Yes.
نعم.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Go, go, go, go!
إنطلق إنطلق إنطلق إنطلق!
Hurry up.
أسرع - بسرعة.
I'm rowing.
أنا أجدف.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
A giant panda.
الباندا العملاقة.
Is there really a panda?
هل هناك حقا باندا؟
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
It's too dangerous! Let's run!
انه خطر للغاية!  هيا نركض!
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
It's snowing.
إنها تثلج.
It's so beautiful.
انها جميلة جدا.
It's so cold.
إنه بارد جدا.
Bunny, are you cold?
الأرنب ، هل أنت بارد؟
There are meteors,
هناك شهب
Yes.
نعم.
Make a wish!
تمنى أمنية!
Little rabbit,
أرنب صغير
what wish did you make?
ما هي الرغبة التي صنعتها؟
How can you say your wish?
كيف يمكنك أن تقول أمنيتك؟
All my wishes are about you.
كل أمنياتي عنك.
Little rabbit,
أرنب صغير
you'll catch a cold in such heavy snow.
ستصاب بنزلة برد في مثل هذا الثلج الكثيف.
Come closer to me.
اقترب مني.
Then come closer to me.
ثم اقترب مني.
Su Shengnan,
سو شنغنان ،